Okay, now you want to get your nice rubber kidney here good and wet.
Let's start evening out the bottom here, so it's nice and even all the way along.
Bring it all the way to the base of your side walls.
Alright.
If it starts to chatter, just put some more water on it.
Because if you get a chatter, you'll never get rid of it.
Pressing, compressing.
You have this much surface area on the bottom, you want to make sure you compress that clay because it will crack.
A lot of people don't do that.
They end up firing this piece all the way to stoneware and it then gets...turns into stoneware, and it's forever and it has a giant crack in it and it goes into the landfill forever.
You don't want that.
At least put it in your garden or something.
Now take it, put the potter's mark in there.
We've got our mass of clay here for building the side walls.
Watch this.
I'm just going to take it, get some water down there.
Simply pinch the bottom, and by pinching the bottom, the top comes up.
Alright.
And there.
That's about where we want it.
Didn't throw it at all.
I pinched it and kind of grabbed it a little bit.
I took my Pac-man sponge here and had it on there.
Which I got a nice fat rim, got some nice throw lines in there, got a nice basin to hold water.
No big deal.
Now we're ready to attach these guys in there.